光是想起来就害怕
It scares us just thinking about it.
你要是听了这个故事 你肯定会觉得我们疯了
When you hear it, you're gonna think we 're insane.
试试看吧 麻烦从头开始
Try us. Please, from the start.
一开始只是小动作
It started out small,
比如手啊 腿啊 与先前的位置不同
like a hand or a leg was in a different position.
然后它的头不是向下看 而是向上看
Then its head was looking up instead of down.
接着有一天 它突然出现在另一个房间
Then one day, it was in a completely different room.
它能四处活动
It was moving around by itself.
有没有可能是有你们
Ever think maybe somebody had a key
公寓钥匙的人的恶作剧呢
to your apartment and was playing a trick on you?
我们以前也是这么想
That's exactly what we thought.
(安娜贝拉案件 1968年)
但是我们从没发现有人进来过的痕迹
But never once did we find any sign or evidence of intrusion.
所以你们都认为这个娃娃被鬼怪附体
And this all led you to believe that the doll was possessed?
是的
Yes.
之前 Camilla 联系过一个灵媒
Camilla got in touch with a medium.
她说有一个七岁小女孩
We learned from her that a 7 year old girl..
叫 Annabelle Higgins 死在这公寓
..Named Annabelle Higgins had died in this apartment.
她很孤单 也很喜欢我的娃娃
She was lonely and took a liking to my doll.
她只是想和我们做朋友
All she wanted was to be friends.
当我们听了之后 很同情她
When we heard this, we felt really sorry for her.
我是说 我们是护士 就应该帮助他人
I mean, we're nurses, we help people.
所以
So..
我们就同意她附身在这个娃娃上
..We gave her permission to move into the doll.
等等 你们做了什么
Wait, you did what?
她想通过附身在这娃娃上 和我们在一起
She wanted to live with us by inhabiting the doll.
我们同意了
We said yes.
但是 从那时起 情况变得糟糕起来
But then things got worse.
天啊
God.
我们回家时 她就坐在走廊上
When we came home, she was sitting in the hallway.
但是我们把她放在客房的
But we had left her in the spare room.
Debbie Debbie 等等
Debbie! Debbie, wait!
我们吓蒙了
We are beyond terrified.
我们不知道这是怎么了 也不知道该怎么做 你们能帮我们吗
We don't know what's going on or what to do. Can you help us?
我们能
Yes, we can.
不过 首先 根本没有个叫
Now, firstly, there's no
Annabelle的女孩 也从未存在过
such thing as Annabelle, and there never was.
鬼怪也没有这样的能力
Ghosts don't possess such power.
我认为这东西有极强的操纵能力
I think what we have here is something extremely manipulative.
非人类的东西
It's something inhuman.
你们承认这个娃娃的身份是个大错
It was a big mistake acknowledging this doll.
正因如此 你们才会被这鬼神怪力作弄
And through that, the inhuman spirit tricked you.
是你们默许了它侵扰你们的生活
You gave it permission to infest your lives.
这鬼神怪力是什么
What's an inhuman spirit?
它不会以人类的形式存在在地球上
It's something that's never walked the earth in human form.
它是恶魔的存在
It's something demonic.
这么说 娃娃没有被附体
So the doll was never possessed?
没有 它只是一个媒介
No, no, it was used as a conduit.
它出现在各处 造成一种被附体的假象
It was moved around to give the impression of possession.
恶魔只附体于人 而非物
Demonic spirits don't possess things, they possess people.
你们 才是它的目标
It wanted to get inside of you.
好了 可以了 Drew 关了吧
All right, that's good, Drew. You can shut it down now.
开灯
Hit the lights.
然后我们让教堂派了一位牧师去赐福
So we got the church to send a priest over perform
于这间房子和它的主人
to bless the house and the occupants.
不管之前是什么在侵扰这间公寓
Whatever was oppressing that apartment
都已离他们远去 有什么问题吗
was no longer with them. Any questions?
就你吧
Yes.
那娃娃现在在哪里
Where's the doll now?
一个安全的地方
Someplace safe.
- 这位 - 你们到底是干什么的
- Yep. - So, what are you guys?
我是说人们怎么称呼你们
I mean, what do people call you?
这个嘛 有人叫过我们鬼神学家
Uh, well, we've been called Demonologists.
这是其中一个
That's one name for us.
捉鬼人 超自然研究者
Ghost hunters, paranormal researchers.
奇葩
Kooks.
疯子
Wackos.
还是更喜欢人们叫我们Ed和Lorraine Warren
But we prefer to be known simply as Ed and Lorraine Warren.
二十世纪60年代起 Ed和Lorraine Warren就被奉为世界上最富盛名的超自然研究者
Lorraine天生拥有敏锐的洞察力而Ed只是一名被天主教堂承认的未受戒的鬼神学家
贯穿他们饱受争议的职业生涯的几千起案件中有这么一起如此恶意满满致使他们保密至今
基于真实故事
《招魂》
(1971年 哈利斯维尔 罗德岛)
我们到了
Here we are.
听到了吗
Wow, hear that?
- 什么都没有听到 - 没错
- I don't hear anything. - Exactly.
- 好了 小家伙们 我们到了 - 从车里出来
- Okay. Guys, we are here! - Get out of the car.
天啊 这里真是偏僻
Oh, God, we're in the middle of nowhere.
- 你们兴奋吗  - 快回答是 - 是
- Are you excited? - Where's my "Yes"? Where's my "Yes"? - Yes!
来赛跑
I'll race you!
- 你们不兴奋吗 - 兴奋啦
- Are you guys excited? - Yes!
我好兴奋 来啊 Sadie
I'm so excited! Come on, Sadie!
我要有自己的房间
I get my own room!
别闹了 不准
Are you kidding me? No dibs on the rooms!
什么
What? What?
我能自己选房间吗
So do I get to pick my own room?
还是连这我也没有选择
Or do I have no choice in that either?
只要遇到一个小帅哥 她就会忘了Jersey
Well, first cute boy she meets, she'll forget about Jersey.
好吧 我希望
Great. I hope.
我都等不及了
I can't wait.
来吧 Sadie
Come on, Sadie.
Sadie 来
Sadie, let's go.
嘿 走啊
Hey, come.
你怎么了啊
What's the matter with you?
走啊 姑娘
Hey, come on, girl.
好吧 你就待着吧
All right, suit yourself.
小心脚下
Watch your step.
借过借过
Coming through.
小心 爸爸
Whoa, watch out, Dad.
- 这个你想放哪儿 - 放客厅
- Where do you want it? - They go to the living room.
Andrea 我的风铃呢
Andrea, where's my wind chime?
Nancy大概放那房间了
I think Nancy's got it in the other room.
谢谢 Nancy 你看到我的风铃了吗
Thanks. Hey, Nancy, have you seen my wind chime?
- 这个吗 - 对 谢谢
- Oh, this one? - Yeah, thanks.
- 你得够得着 - Nancy 放手 给我
- You're gonna have to catch it. - Nancy! Let go! Give it here.
你真讨厌
You're so mean.
妈妈 我能把风铃挂起来吗
Hey, Mom, can I hang up my wind chime?
当然 外面有条绳儿 你挂那儿
Of course. There's a line outside you can hang it on.
亲爱的 让April进来 天都要黑了
Honey, have April come in, okay? It's gonna be dark soon.
好
Okay.
过来 April 妈妈让我们进去
Come on, April! Mom wants us inside!
Cindy 看看我找到了什么
Look what I found, Cindy.
一
One..
二
..Two..
三
..Three.
走 走 走 不准都看
Come on, come on, come on. No peeking.
四
Four.
披萨你们这样就算吃完了啊 别浪费啊
Are you guys done with the pizza? I don't want it going to waste.
- 我们快走 - 养女儿可真贵
- Let's go. - It's expensive feeding you girls.
七 八 九 十
Seven, eight, nine, ten.
我躲哪儿
Where should I hide?
好了没 我来了啊
Ready or not, here I come!
好了 拍手
Okay, clap.
你们不熟悉这房子
You don't know the house well enough.
- 有人会受伤的 - 我没事 没事
- Someone's gonna get hurt. - I'm okay, I'm okay.
再拍一次手
Second clap.
作弊了啊
That's cheating.
拍手
Clap.
抓到你了
Got You!
- 你还好吗 - 还好
- Are you okay? -Um.. Yeah.
好吧 又弄坏啥了
All right, what did we break now?
- 我不是有意的 - 出去 拜托
- I didn't mean to. - Move out of there, please.
是Christine的错
It was Christine's fault.
- 上帝啊 - 我的错 天啊
- Oh, jeez. - My fault? Oh, my God.
- Christine干的 - 不是我干的
- Christine did it. - No, I didn't.
- 你推了我 - 不 是你自己往后跌倒的
- You pushed me. -No, no, you fell back.
Nancy 能帮我拿些火柴吗
Hey, Nancy, can you go get me the matches, please?
怎么回事
What's going on?
- Nancy打破东西了 - 闭嘴 - 是你干的
- Nancy broke something. - Shut up. - It was you.
- 什么坏了啊 - 墙坏了
- What broke? - It's the Wall.
我想我们有个地窖还是啥的
I think we have a cellar or something.
- 让我看看 - 小心 好吧 - 让开 让开
- I wanna see, I wanna see. - Watch out. Okay. - Move, move, move.
这里 火柴 谢谢
Here, matches. Thank you.
- 我想看看 - 会看到的
- I wanna see. - You can see.
- 我想看嘛 - 都看得到
- I wanna see. - You can all see.
让开
Move!
哦 天啊
Oh, man.
Roger
Roger?
下面有什么
What do you see down there?
一时说不清楚
Just, uh, hard to tell, you know?
一架老式钢琴 一堆垃圾
It's an old piano and a whole bunch of garbage.
啊 可恶
Agh. Son of a..
Rog
Rog?
上来
Come on up.
女孩子别下去了
I don't want you girls going down there.
- 下面都是蜘蛛 - 恶心
- That place is loaded with spiders. - Ew!
放松 没事
Just relax. Okay.
别闹了 Nancy 不好玩
Stop it, Nancy. It's not funny.
总之多了额外的建筑面积
We've got extra square footage anyway.
明早我再看看
I'll check it out in the morning.
- 为啥用木板封住啊 - 不知道
- I wonder why it was boarded up. - I don't know.
孩子们 游戏结束了
Okay, guys, show's over.
- 再玩五分钟 - 不能多了
- Five minutes. - No more minutes.
- 上床睡觉 拜托 谢谢配合 - 都去睡觉
- Up to bed. Please. Thank you. - All right to bed.
天啊 累死了
Man, I'm fried.
Sadie怎么回事
Something's up with Sadie.
是啊 不知道她啥毛病
Yeah, I don't know what her problem is.
死活不进门
Couldn't get her to come inside.
不能留她在外过夜啊
We can't leave her out there.
她没事的 给她上链子了
She's all right. I got her on a chain.
Sadie 安静点
Sadie, hey, be quiet.
谢谢你做的一切
Thanks for making this work.
我知道你割舍了不少
I know it was a lot to bite off.
会很棒的 对吧
It's gonna be great, isn't it?
我觉得已经很好了
I think it's great already.
是啊
Yeah.
你是不是太累 不能给新家来一次洗礼
You still too fried to christen the new house?
谁说我累了
Who said I'm fried?
- 没人觉得累 - 哈哈
- Ain't nobody here's fried. - Ha, ha.
妈
Mom?
睡得怎样啊
Hey. How did you guys sleep?
我好冷
I'm cold.
是有点凉
It is chilly, isn't it?
我们就不能有个
You think maybe we could have
卫生间能用的房子吗
bought a house with a toilet that actually works?
跟你爸爸说
Tell your father.
还有昨晚我屋里
And there was a funky smell
有股恶臭 闻起来像死尸
in my room last night. Rip like something died.
- 还有吗现在 - 没了
- Is it still there? - No.
问题解决了啊
Problem solved.
Roger
Roger?
我在下面 亲爱的
Down here, honey.
早啊
Morning.
清理这些可得费不少力啊
This is gonna take some serious elbow grease.
是啊
Yeah.
天啊
Oh, my God.
这些东西怎么处理啊
What are we gonna do with all this stuff?
我们得仔细翻一遍
Well, we probably ought to go through it, you know?
也许会有不少值钱的古董呢
There might be some antiques down here worth a lot money.
也或许是一堆前主人都不想要的垃圾
Yeah, or just a lot of junk the previous owner didn't want.
- 现在都是我们的了 - 别客气
- It's ours now. - Knock yourself out.
- 我去煮点咖啡 - 好
- I'm gonna make some coffee. - Okay.
我折腾折腾看这炉子还能用不
I'm gonna see if I can get this furnace working.
真是太好了 冻死了
Yeah, that'd be nice. It's freezing.
是啊
Yeah.
Sadie 过来 Sadie
Sadie! Come here, Sadie!
妈咪
Mommy!
妈咪 Sadie 在哪啊
Mommy, where's Sadie?
她在外面呢 我想
She's outside. You know, I'm sure
她一定饿了 你去找找她吧
she's hungry by now. Why don't you go and get her.
- 喔 - 早 爸爸
- Whoa. - Morning, Dad.
- 你能拿着这个吗 - 好
- Can you hold this? - Sure.
- Sadie - 慢点 Scoot
- Sadie! - Slow it down, Scoot.
- Roger - 咋了
- Roger. - Yeah.
这个钟停在3:07 走廊的那个也是
This clock stopped at 3:07, and so did the one in the hallway.
怪事了
That's weird.
可能走着的时候被粗暴对待了
Maybe it got knocked around in the move.
说到粗暴 昨晚你对我做了什么
Speaking of knocked around, what did you do to me last night?
- 啊 不是我干的啊 是我吗 - 我不知道
- Ouch. I didn't do that. Did I? - I don't know.
Sadie
Sadie!
April April
April! April!
怎么了 April 怎么回事
What's... April! What's going on?
- 怎么了 - 天啊
- What happened? - Oh, my God!
哦 Sadie
Oh, Sadie.
(门罗 康尼狄克州 Warren的房子)
东西我们都锁在这里了
We keep everything locked in here.
随便看看吧
Feel free to look around.
别乱碰
Just don't touch anything.
太神奇了
This is crazy.
都是你们调查案件里的物件
So all these are taken from cases you've investigated?
是的
That's right.
每件你看到的 不是闹过鬼 就是被诅咒过
Everything you see in here is either haunted, cursed..
要么就是某些仪式中用到的物件
..Or has been used in some kind of ritualistic practice.
可不是什么玩具
Nothing's a toy.
那个玩具猴也不是
Not even the toy monkey.
别碰
Don't touch it.
这吓人吗 或者说你不担心吗
Oh, ahem. Well, isn't it scary, or doesn't it worry you..
屋里有这些东西
..To have all these items right in your home?
所以我们每个月
That's why we have a priest
都找个牧师来这里赐福
that comes by once a month to bless the room.
我是这么想的
Well, the way I see it is:
把这些放在这里比在外面更安全
It's safer for these things to be in here than out there.
类似让枪支远离街道的道理
It's kind of like keeping guns off the street.
为啥不直接把它们丢进焚化炉 毁了
Why not just throw them in an incinerator? Destroy them.
这样破坏的只是容器
Well, that would only destroy the vessel.
有时候 把它们封印在瓶子里更好些
Sometimes it's better to keep the genie in the bottle.
那么 安娜贝拉娃娃也在这里
Say, is the, uh, Annabelle doll here?
这边请
Right this way.
好
Yeah.
- 你说它只是一个媒介 - 是的
- You said she's a conduit? - That's right.
什么意思
What does that mean?
一个强大的恶魔将自己封于其中
A very powerful demonic has latched itself onto her.
那么你们调查这些闹鬼事件时
So when you guys investigate these hauntings..
如何避免它们附身在你们身上呢
..How do you stop them from latching onto you?
我们得提高警惕
We have to take great precaution.
那你妻子呢
But what about your wife?
她怎么了
What about her?
Gordon神父告诉我...
Well, Father Gordon told me that..
那不是一回事
Well, that was different.
那是在驱魔的时候发生的
What happened to my wife happened during an exorcism.
有何不同
Well, what's the difference?
稍等一下
Excuse me.
宝贝儿 你干嘛呢
Honey, what are you doing?
过来
Come here.
懂事点 好吗
You know better. All right?
Georgiana
Georgiana?
- 过来 你碰了什么吗 - 没
- Come on. Did you touch anything? - No.
好 过来 亲爱的
All right, come on, honey.
- Georgiana 你能带Judy上楼吗 - 好
- Georgiana! Could you take Judy upstairs? - Oh, sure.
不管怎样 你都不能进这个房间 记得吗
You can't go into this room, no matter what, remember?
- 是 爸爸 - 好
- Yes, Daddy. - All right.
- 走吧 - 好 来吧
- Go on. - Okay, come on.
去给你弄点零食吃 好吗 走吧
Let's see if I can find you a little snack, okay? Come on.
嘿 怎么了
Hey. What's going on in here?
- 爸爸 看我 - 很好看啊
- Daddy, look. - You look very pretty.
好了 弄好了 换衣服吃饭去
All right, all done. Go get dressed for dinner.
- 我就穿这个吃饭 - 不行
- I'm wearing it to dinner. - No, you're not!
给你
Here you go.
怎样
How'd it go?
他应该会写一篇正面报道吧
Oh, I think he may write a positive article.
是个容易轻信的人啊
Ooh, a non-skeptic.
不错的改变
That's a pleasant change.
是啊
Yeah.
别再责怪你自己了
Stop blaming yourself.
没放糖
No sugar.
马上回来
Be right back.
别闹了 Nancy
Not funny, Nancy.
什么
What?
别抓我的脚
Stop grabbing my foot.
闭嘴 我什么都没做
Shut up, I didn't do anything.
嗯 是啊
Yeah, right.
别放屁了
And stop farting.
真的很臭
It really stinks.
别什么都怪我 明明是你
Don't blame that on me. It's you. Pew.
爸爸
Dad?
Andrea 你不睡觉在干什么
Andrea, what are you doing out of bed?
什么声音
What's that sound?
是Cindy 她在我房间 她又梦游了
It's Cindy. She's in my room. She's sleepwalking again.
她之前没这样过啊
I've never seen her do this before.
我记得你说 她梦游时别弄醒她
I remembered you saying not to wake her if she's like this.
不 我们只是把她放回床上
No, we just put her back to bed.
嘿嘿 宝贝 嘘
Hey, hey. Sweetie. Shh.
我们回床上去
Let's go back to bed.
她没事了 晚安
She's okay. Good night.
晚安
Night.
她又梦游了 她好久没这样了
She's sleepwalking again? She hasn't done that for a while.
她最后跑Andrea房里了
She ended up in Andrea's room too.
好像有点吓着她了
I think kind of freaked her out.
- 这不太好 我们该怎么办 - 我不知道
- That's not good. What are we gonna do? - I don't know.
- 亲爱的 你怎么又有新的瘀伤了 - 啥
- Honey, you got another bruise here.-  Hmm?
疼吗
Does that hurt?
奇怪了
That's weird.
我不知道 你去看看医生吧
I don't know. Will you do me a favor, go see a doctor for that?
- 好 我会的 驾车安全 - 嗯
- Yeah, I will. Drive safe. - Yeah.
- 我爱你 - 我也爱你
- I love you. - I love you too.
拜拜
Bye!
爱你们
Love you!
- Cindy 午饭吃了吗 - 吃了
- Cindy, you have your - lunch? Yeah.
是的 的确是
Yes, I do.
我好想Sadie
I miss Sadie a lot.
她是我最好的朋友
She was my best friend.
你也是我的朋友 对吧
You're my friend, right?
嗯 那我们一起玩吧
Yeah, let's play.
- 你在和谁说话 - Rory
- Who are you talking to? - Rory.
Rory
Rory?
- 他是我的新朋友 - 是吗
- He's my new friend. - Oh, really?
- 你想见见他吗 - 想 怎么见
- Yeah, do you want to see him? - Yeah. Uhhuh. How?
用这个
With this.
当音乐停止
When the music stops,
在镜子里你会看到他在你身后
you see him in the mirror standing behind you.
好
Okay.
但是你要拧这钥匙
But you have to twist the key.
好
Okay.
- 嘣 妈咪  - 哈哈
Boo, Mommy! Oh! Haha!
- April 差点让你吓出心脏病 - 吓着你了
- April, you just gave me a heart attack. - Got you!
嗯 好吧 我想Rory不想见我 是吧
Well, okay, I guess Rory doesn't want to see me, huh?
嗯
Hmm. Oh, well.
我们玩瞎子摸鱼吗
Can we play hide and clap?
瞎子摸鱼 亲爱的 我不太想玩
Hide and clap... Oh, honey, I don't want to play.
- 求你了 他们都不让我玩 - 好吧
- Please! Nobody ever lets me play. - Okay, okay.
记住啊 你能让我拍手三次
Remember, you get to ask me for three claps.
好
Okay.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
- 我去躲了 - 好
- I'm gonna go hide now! -  Okay.
四 五
Four, five..
六 七
..Six, seven..
八 九
..Eight, nine..
十
..Ten!
第一次拍手
First clap!
哦 可恶
Ow. Shit.
再一次拍手
Second clap!
April
April.
哦 我知道你躲在哪里了
Oh, I know where you're hiding.
最后拍一次
Give me the third clap.
我要找到你了
I'm gonna get you now.
我听到你呼吸了
I can hear you breathing.
April
April.
你把布条摘下来了 我赢了
Ha, ha. You took your blindfold off. I win!
你差太远了 我在Christine Nancy房里呢
You weren't even warm, Mom. I was in Christine and Nancy's room.
你得给我些活儿
I gotta have some routes here,
不然我卡车的保险就要没了
or I'm gonna lose the insurance on the rig.
这才我一半的价钱
That's like half of my rate, man.
好吧
Yeah, okay.
好 我接了
I'll, uh.. Yeah, I'll take it.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 到哪儿  - 佛罗里达州
- What's the route? - It's, uh, Florida.
来回一周 我明天出发
It's a week turnaround. I start tomorrow.
我们会挺过去的
We'll get through this.
嗯
Yeah.
睡觉去吧
Come on, let's go to bed.
住手 Nancy 这一点儿也不好玩
Stop it, Nancy. It's not funny anymore.
我要睡了 别抓我的脚了
I'm trying to sleep, please stop grabbing my feet.
Nancy
Nancy?
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
Christine
Christine?
你没事吧
Are you all right?
你看见了吗
Do you see it?
看见什么
See what?
门背后有人
There's someone behind the door.
什么
What?
有个人站在那儿
There's someone standing over there.
没有人啊
I don't see anyone.
在盯着我们看呢
It's looking right at us.
Nancy 别去 Nancy
Nancy, don't! Nancy.
不 你看
No, no. Look. Look.
这儿没人 看见了吗
Look, there's no one here. See?
噢 又是那股味道
Ugh. It's that smell again.
神啊
Oh, my God.
他就站在你后面
It's standing right behind you.
Christine Christine Christine
Christine?! Christine! Christine!
天啊 打不开
God, it won't op..
Christine 不 不 不
Christine! No! No! No!
- 怎么了 发生了什么  - 有人在这儿
- What's going on? What happened? - There was someone else in here!
啥 哪儿
What? Where?
门那里 他刚才在门后面
By the door. It was behind the door.
亲爱的 这儿什么也没有 没人在这儿
Honey, there's nothing in here. There's nobody in here.
有别人在这儿
There was someone else in here!
我在睡觉 然后有人在抓我的脚
I was just sleeping, and then I felt somebody grab my feet.
我以为是Nancy
So I thought it was Nancy.
亲爱的 我敢肯定只是噩梦而已
Well, honey, I'm pretty sure that it was just a bad dream.
不 他跟我说话了
No! It talked to me!
他说
It said..
他想要我们一家人都死掉
..That it wants my family dead.
Winston先生
Mr. Winston!
Winston Winston
Winston? Winston?
到他后面去
Get behind him.
你去哪儿
Where you off to?
我去商店买点东西
I just gotta run to the store for a few things.
- 想都别想 - 你在说什么
- Why do you even try? - What? What do you mean?
十五年了 你有骗到过我吗
In 15 years have you ever been able to lie to me?
Gordon神父来电话 有个案子想让我们看看
Father Gordon called. He's got a case he wants us to look into.
我说我自己去看看 Lorraine 就我自己
I said I'd go check it out myself. Lorraine, myself.
我跟你一起去
I'm going with you.
我知道你担心那件事会重演
I know you're worried it's gonna happen again.
没错 我担心 我很担心
Yeah, I am. I really am.
或许我们该隐退一阵 写本书
Maybe it's just time we take a break. Write that book.
还记得我们结婚那天晚上你对我说的话吗
Do you remember what you said to me on our wedding night?
"能再来一次吗"
"Can we do it again?"
后面那句
After that.
你说上帝让我们走到一起是有原因的 对吧
You said that God brought us together for a reason. Right?
我很确定不是为了写书
I'm pretty sure it's not to write a book.
我去换衣服
I'm gonna get dressed.
我们认为问题出在阁楼
We've isolated the disturbances to the attic.
你们来听听看
I want you to listen for a second.
天啊 就是这个声音
Oh, my God, that's it.
再来一次 Ed
Do it again, Ed.
现在还只是我在施重
Right now it's just my weight.
当水流经管道
But you take the water coming off the pipe..
加上风从破掉的窗户吹进来
..Combined with the wind coming through the broken window..
这些木板会胀开并且相互挤压
..These boards are gonna expand and rub against each other.
整栋屋子都能听见
You heard it all through the house
是因为这些管子连着暖气
because of these pipes leading to the radiator.
所以这屋子没有闹鬼
So this place isn't haunted?
不 很少是
No, it rarely is.
通常都是有科学的解释的
Yeah, there's usually always some kind of rational explanation.
(Carolyn Perron 一天两次 用于铁质缺乏)
孩子们 早过了上床的时间了
Girls, it's way past your bedtime.
谁
Who is that?
不管谁在下面 我要把你锁在里面了
Who's ever down there, I'm gonna lock you in now!
救命
Help!
Andrea 救命
Andrea! Help!
嘿 想玩瞎子摸鱼吗
Hey, wanna play hide and clap?
Cindy
Cindy?
好吧
Okay, now..
过来
All right?
来吧
All right, come on.
来
Come on.
来这边
There you go.
你今晚就和我一起睡吧
Okay, you can just sleep with me tonight, all right?
来
There you go.
乖
There.
- Andrea  - 救命 救命 救命
- Andrea?  - Help! Help! Help!
- 谁在这儿  - Andrea
- Who's in here?  - Andrea!
Andrea Andrea
Andrea? Andrea!
这边
In here!
救命 爸爸 救命 是Andrea
Help, Daddy! Help, it's Andrea!
- 谁在这儿  - Andrea
- Who's in here?  - Andrea!
发生了什么
What happened?
神啊 有人能来告诉我发生了什么吗
Somebody, goddamn it, tell me what's going on here?
恐惧 其定义为一种
Fear is defined as a feeling
不安及焦虑的情绪 由已经出现
of agitation and anxiety caused by the presence..
或是将要出现的危险引起
..Or imminence of danger.
不论是鬼魂 灵体 或是某种实体 都以它为食
Whether it's a ghost, a spirit or an entity, they all feed on it.
比如这位Maurice
Take Maurice here.
法裔加拿大人
A French-Canadian farmer
受教育水平不超过三年级
with no more than a thirdgrade education..
但他被附身以后
..Yet after he was possessed,
他说的拉丁语是我听过的最好的
spoke some of the best Latin I'd ever heard.
有时候还能倒着说
Sometimes backwards.
他曾被他父亲猥亵
He'd been molested by his father,
反复虐待
who had also tortured him repeatedly.
一个恶灵在这个人身体里安了家
A dark spirit made its home in this man.
如果你看着他的眼睛 你会发现他在泣血
Now, if you look into his eyes, you can see him tearing blood.
并且
And like that..
一个倒十字从他的体内浮现出来
..An upsidedown cross started to appear from within his body.
Drew 你可以把灯打开了
All right, Drew, you can hit the lights.
你有亲自进行过驱魔吗
Did you personally perform the exorcism?
没有 我没有权力 但我协助参与过许多次
No, I'm not authorized. But I've assisted on many.
驱魔仪式可能是很危险的
See, an exorcism can be very dangerous..
不仅仅是受害者 每个在屋子里的人都是如此
..Not only for the victim, but for anyone in the room.
- Maurice怎么了  - 他试图杀死他的妻子
- What happened to Maurice?  - He tried to kill his wife..
但是他射伤了她的手臂
..But instead shot her in
然后把枪指向了自己
the arm and then turned the gun on himself.
Maurice的一生坎坷而无望
Maurice had a very troubled life with little to live for..
即使是一位驱魔师也没能救他
..And not even an exorcist could bring him back.
让我们看看魔鬼行为的三个阶段
Which brings us to the three stages of demonic activity:
侵染 压迫 和附身
Infestation, oppression and possession.
首先 侵染
Now, infestation:
低语声 脚步
That's the whispering, the footsteps,
感觉到有别人存在
the feeling of another presence..
然后发展为压迫 即第二阶段
..Which ultimately grows into oppression, the second stage.
这个阶段 受害者
Now this is where the victim, and it's usually the one..
通常是心理最为脆弱的那个人
..Who's the most psychologically vulnerable..
会成为外来力量的目标
..Is targeted specifically by an external force.
让受害者崩溃 摧毁他们的意志
Breaks the victim down. Crushes their will.
等到受害者陷入虚弱的状态
And, once in a weakened state,
就会进入第三个阶段 附身
leads them to the third and final stage: possession.
- 嗨 Ed Lorraine  - 嗯
- Hey, Ed? Lorraine?  - Yeah.
有人想和你们谈谈
There's someone here that would like to talk to you.
- 嗨  - 谢谢 Drew
- Hi.  - Thanks, Drew.
- 谢谢 - 再见
- Thank you.  - I'll see you later.
有什么能帮到你的吗
How can we help you?
我们家里发生了可怕的事情
There's something horrible happening in my house.
能请你们过来看看吗
Could you come and take a look?
时间有点晚了
You know, uh, it's getting kinda late.
- 我们得回家 - 你不明白状况
- We really need to head to our family. - No. You don't understand.
我们明白 一般都有科学的解释
But we do. There's usually some sort of rational explanation..
我的五个女儿都快被吓死了
I have five daughters who are scared to death.
我真很怕这东西会伤害我们
I'm so afraid this thing wants to hurt us.
你们也有一个女儿
You have a daughter.
你们不会竭尽所能地去保护她吗 拜托了
Wouldn't you do anything you could to protect her? Please.
请你们过来看看吧
Please can you come and take a look?
好 我们去
Of course,we will.
我们会去的
Of course, we will.
Jan 把门打开
Come on, Jan! Open up!
Jan 怎么了
Jan, what happened?
你头上怎么变黑了
The top of your head turned black.
快起来
You guys straighten up? Thanks.
别傻了 这是假发
Don't be silly, it's a wig.
- 你好  - 你好
- Hello. Hi. - Hi. Hi.
谢谢你们能来
Thanks for coming.
- 嗨 我是Roger  - 我是Lorraine
- Hi, I'm Roger.  - Lorraine.
很高兴认识你 Roger 我是Ed Warren
Hey, nice to meet you, Roger. Ed Warren.
- 谢谢你们能来  - 请进
- Thanks for coming.  - Please, come in.
谢谢
Thank you.
那么
So..
天啊 看看你们 这些小美人是谁啊
Oh, my God. Look at you all. Who are these beautiful young women?
这是Andrea 她是最大的 Nancy Cindy Christine
This is Andrea, the oldest, Nancy, Cindy, Christine..
还有April
..And April.
这是Warren先生和太太
It's Mr. And Mrs. Warren.
我们现在都睡在下面
We're all sleeping down here now. Mm.
孩子们觉得这样更安全 也更暖和
The girls feel safer and it's warmer.
我一直在把暖气开大
I'm constantly turning up the heat,
但这房子始终冷得要死
but the house is always freezing.
不是炉子的问题
It's not a problem with the furnace.
至少我没有发现
I mean, not that I can find.
过去的几夜情况更加糟糕
It's gotten a lot worse the past few nights.
还有股奇怪的味道 像是腐烂的肉
There's this awful smell, like rotting meat.
房子里到处都能闻到
It moves around the house.
怎么了 什么情况
What? What is it?
酸臭味有时象征着某种恶魔活动
Well, rancid smells could indicate some type of demonic activity.
天啊
Oh, my God.
这是为了防止这些门在夜里发出声音
That's to keep those doors from banging at night.
不然的话 一整夜都会像这样
Otherwise, it's like: All night long, just like that.
- 每次三下吗  - 是的
- Does it come in threes?  - Yeah.
到天亮结束
It stops at dawn?
没错
Uh-huh.
这是对三位一体的侮辱
Well, sometimes it's meant as an insult to the Trinity:
圣父 圣子 圣灵
The Father, the Son and the Holy Spirit.
最糟糕的是
You know, it's the damndest thing,
有各种各样的鸟
but we also get all kinds of birds..
会撞到房子上
..That will just fly against
撞断它们的脖子
the side of the house and break their necks.
是吗
Hm. Really?
钟会在凌晨三点零七的时候停下
And the clocks stop at 3:07 a.M.
- 全都这样吗  - 所有
- All of them?  - Every one.
我们本来把这些照片沿楼梯挂着
Oh, we were hanging those along the stairs.
一直有什么东西把它们打下来
Something just kept knocking them down,
所以我们就不挂了
so we stopped hanging them up.
这就是我之前说的
That's what I was talking about.
我们搬进来的时候就在这儿了
It was here when we moved in.
地窖里也有很多东西
There's also a lot of stuff in the cellar.
让我看看地窖
Show me the cellar.
看看她都逼我做了什么
Look what she made me do.
你感觉到什么了吗 亲爱的
You picking up anything in here, hon?
这儿发生过一些很可怕的事情
Something awful happened here, Ed.
那些淤青是来这里后出现的吗
Those bruises, they from something that happened here?
是我有些缺铁
Oh, it's some iron deficiency thing I have.
发生了这么多事
You know, with all that's been going on,
你们为什么还没有搬走呢
why haven't you just moved out?
我不知道我们能搬到哪里去
I don't know where we'd move to, you know?
我们所有的钱
We got all our money tied up in
都套在这房子上了 修理也费了不少钱
this place and had a lot of repairs on top of that.
我也不知道谁会
And I don't know anybody whose
收留一家不知会待多久的七口人
gonna take in a family of seven indefinitely.
所以我们找到了你们
That's why we tracked you down.
我们很高兴 你们找了我们
We're glad you found us.
我们开始吧
All right, let's get started.
我是Ed Warren 今天是一九七一年十一月一号
My name is Ed Warren. It's November 1st, 1971.
和我在一起的是Carolyn Perron
I'm sitting here with Carolyn Perron..
她和她的家人
..Who, with her family,
正在经历超自然事件
has been experiencing supernatural occurrences.
请讲吧
Okay, go ahead.
从哪儿开始呢
Where do I start?
从最先发生的事开始
From the first occurrence.
我想应该是那些钟
I guess it was the clocks.
你爸妈告诉我你有个朋友
Mom and Dad tell me that you have a friend.
他的名字叫Rory 他也住在这
His name's Rory. He lives here too.
- 嗯  - 但他总是很难过
- Hmm.  - But he's always sad.
为什么呢
Why is that?
他不告诉我 但我想他遇到过很不好的事
He won't tell me but I think something bad happened to him.
我能见见Rory吗
Do you mind if I try to see Rory?
怎么了
What is it?
我们是从银行的拍卖会上买来的
We bought it at auction from the bank,
所以我们一直不知道谁在这儿住过
so, you know, we never knew who lived here.
Lorraine和我
Well, Lorraine and I both
认为你们的房子需要净化
feel that what your house needs is a cleansing.
一次驱魔
An exorcism.
什么 驱魔
What, exorcism?
我以为那是对人做的
I thought that was something that you do to people.
不 并不一定
No, not necessarily, no.
我们得离开这儿
We have to get out of here.
恐怕这样做没什么用
I'm afraid that's not gonna help.
Lorraine看见了一些东西
Lorraine saw something, which..
说吧 亲爱的
Go ahead, hon.
我看见个邪物萦绕在你们房子周围
I've been seeing the dark entity that haunts your house..
和这块土地
..And your land.
第一次是进门的时候
I saw it first when I came through your door.
它附在你的身后
It was latched to your back.
然后我又看见
And then I saw it again with
它在孩子们身后 在我进客厅的时候
the girls when we walked into the living room.
不管你们去哪里
And it doesn't matter where you go..
这邪物已经紧紧地附在了你们一家身上
..This dark entity has latched itself to your family..
在侵蚀着你们
..And it's feeding off you.
即使我们离开
Even if we leave?
有时当你被恶灵缠上 就像是踩到了口香糖
Sometimes when you get haunted, it's like stepping on gum.
它会跟着你
You take it with you.
我得告诉你们 你们这儿有很多魂灵
Look, I gotta tell you, you have a lot of spirits in here..
但这一个我最为担心
..But this is the one that I'm
因为它怨气极重
most worried about, because it is so hateful.
那我们怎么办 我们能叫牧师来吗
Okay, so what do we do? Can we call a priest?
我也希望可以这么简单
I wish it were that easy.
驱魔是一种古老的仪式
Performing an exorcism is an archaic procedure.
需要多年的训练
Requires years of training.
即便如此 也会出可怕的差错
And even then, I have seen it go horribly wrong.
但在那之前
But before we even get that far,
还必须经由教会的同意
the church has to authorize it first.
这就意味着我们必须要先调查
It means we gotta investigate,
取证并提供证明
gather evidence and provide proof..
这才是困难的步骤
..And that's the hard part.
你们的孩子洗礼过了吗
Have your children been baptized?
不 我们不太有时间
Uh, no, we never got around to that.
我们家并不怎么去教堂
We're not really a churchgoing family.
你或许要重新考虑下了
Well, you may want to rethink that.
我们的到访可能会让事情更糟
Our presence here could make things worse.
为什么
Why?
因为我们是威胁
Because we're a threat.
不管你们遇到的是啥 肯定不会喜欢我们
And whatever you're dealing with here isn't gonna like us.
目前为止它还没有暴力行为 这是好事
So far it hasn't done anything violent, and that's a good sign.
所以我们的人会做些这地方的调查
So we're gonna have our guy do some homework on the property..
好看看我们对付的是什么
..To see what we're up against.
Judy 什么事儿呀
Judy, what are you up to?
- 我有礼物要给你  - 啊
- I got you a present.  - Aah.
我和奶奶在教堂的跳蚤市场上买来的
Me and Nanna got these at the church's yard sale.
- 亲爱的  - 你一个 我一个
- Honey.  - One for you and one for me.
- 噢  - 她放了一张照片
- Aw.  - She put a picture..
在我这个里面 是你和爸爸的
..Of you and Daddy in mine.
奶奶说这样我们就会一直在一起
Nanna said this way we'll always be together.
你会和我在一起 我也会和你在一起
You'll be with me and I'll be with you.
我想你和爸爸
I miss you and Daddy.
亲爱的
Hey, hon.
怎么了
Yup.
你猜怎么着 Carolyn的声音没录下来
You're not gonna believe this. Carolyn's voice didn't record.
什么意思
What do you mean?
你听
Listen.
我是Ed Warren 今天是一九七一年十一月一号
My name is Ed Warren. It's November 1st, 1971.
和我在一起的是Carolyn Perron
I'm sitting here with Carolyn Perron..
她和她的家人
..Who, with her family,
正经历超自然现象
has been experiencing supernatural occurrences.
请讲吧
Okay, go ahead.
从最先发生的事开始
From the first occurrence.
什么也没录下来
Nothing.
整个录音
The whole time.
- 不知道怎么回事 你发现什么了吗  - 很多
- I don't know. You find anything?  - Lots.
难怪他们会遇到这样的事
I mean, it's no wonder they're going through what they are.
这是最初的样子
That's the original farmhouse.
一八六三年一个叫Jedson Sherman的人盖的
It was built in 1863 by a man named Jedson Sherman..
他娶了一个叫做Bathsheba的女人
..Who was married to a woman named Bathsheba.
Ed 她与Mary Towne Estye有亲属关系
Ed, she's related to Mary Towne Estye.
她是塞勒姆女巫审判中被指控的一员
She was one of the women accused of witchcraft in Salem.
她在游街时被绞死
She was hung during the trials. Wow.
Bathsheba和Jedson结婚后 有了一个孩子
After Bathsheba married Jedson, they had a baby..
在孩子七天大的时候
..And when the baby was 7 days old..
Jedson发现她在壁炉前用孩子做献祭
..Jedson caught her sacrificing it in front of the fireplace.
她跑到码头边的树那里
She ran out to that tree by the dock..
爬了上去 宣称她属于撒旦
..Climbed up, proclaimed her love to Satan..
诅咒了每一个想夺取她土地的人 上吊自杀
..Cursed anyone who tried to take her land, and hung herself.
死亡时间是凌晨三点零七
Time of death was pronounced at 3:07 in the morning.
这就说的通了
Well, that explains a few things.
这个也是
Yeah, so does this.
她姓Walker 三十年代时住在那里
Her last name's Walker. She lived there in the '30s.
她有个儿子叫Rory
She had a boy named Rory
他在树林里神秘失踪了
who mysteriously disappeared in the woods.
而她在地窖里自杀了
Then she killed herself in the cellar.
还不止这些
And that's not all.
原本两百英亩的农场
So, what was the original 200-acre
在那之后被分割并卖掉
farm has since been subdivided and sold off.
有一个男孩淹死在了这个池塘里
There was another boy who drowned in a pond here.
他住的房子 在这边
He lived in a house over here.
一个在附近的家里当
And a woman who worked as a maid
女仆的女孩 她也自杀了
in a neighboring home, she committed suicide too.
夺取她土地的人
People who took her land.
和我在一起的是Carolyn Perron
I'm sitting here with Carolyn Perron..
她和她的家人
..Who, with her family,
正经历超自然事件
has been experiencing supernatural occurrences.
请讲吧
Okay, go ahead.
从最先发生的事开始
From the first occurrence.
Brad来了
Here's Brad.
- 路好找吗  - 嗯
- You find it okay?  - Oh, yeah.
Drew 这是Brad警官
Drew, this is Officer Brad.
Brad Hamilton警官 哈里斯维尔 罗得岛警局
Officer Brad Hamilton, Harrisville, Rhode Island P.D.
很高兴见到你
Hm. Nice to meet you, man.
- 你就是那位幸运的新警察 是吧  - 是吧
- So you're the lucky new cop, huh?  - Guess so.
你知道你不能拿枪打鬼的吧
You know you can't shoot ghosts, right?
别逗他了 Drew
Take it easy on him, Drew.
来 帮我把这些卸下来
All right, guys, help me get this stuff unloaded.
你拿这个
You take this.
嗨 Roger
Hi, Roger.
这里弄完
All right. When you're finished here,
你就去弄楼上吧 Drew
why don't you hit upstairs, all right, Drew?
好的
You got it.
这辆雪佛兰哪坏了
What's wrong with the Chevy?
哪没坏
Ugh, what's not wrong with her?
- 要换个汽化器才能启动  - 是吗
Needs a new carburetor to start. Oh, yeah?
看来维修工作得暂停一阵子了
Kind of put fixing her up on hold for a while.
是啊
Yeah. Ahem.
Brad 把恒温器递给我一下
Hey, Brad, hand me a thermostat, would you?
这干嘛用的
What's this, uh, do?
当气温骤然降低的时候
When there's an instant drop in temperature..
恒温器能启动相机拍下照片
..The thermostat triggers the camera to take a picture.
你们真有用这拍到过东西吗
You've actually caught things on film?
有啊 这才是重点
Well, yeah, that's, uh, the point.
为什么要来外面
Why, uh... Why out here?
这是女巫自杀的地方
Well, this is where the witch committed suicide.
她吊死在
She hung herself from that
你头顶那根树干上
branch right above where you're standing.
怎么会有母亲杀死自己的亲生骨肉
How could a mother kill her own child?
对她来说不算孩子
It was never a child to her.
她只是在利用
She just used her Godgiven
上帝赋予的生育能力来反抗上帝
gift as the ultimate offense against him.
女巫认为这能提升她们在撒旦眼中的地位
Witches believe it elevates their status in the eyes of Satan.
那天在沙滩玩的很开心是吧
That's a nice day at the beach, huh?
你怎么知道的
How did you know?
这是种洞悉能力
It's an insight. It's like a
就像从窗帘中窥视他人的生活
peek through the curtain into another person's life.
那天对我意义非凡 我们沿着海岸驾驶
That day meant so much to me. We were driving along the coast.
Nancy说风景很好
Nancy pointed out how pretty the view was.
我认为是拍照的好时机
I thought this is a perfect opportunity for a photo.
我们要重新出发了 你懂 新房子 新起点
We're gonna start fresh, you know? A new house, a new beginning.
你该看见Roger和孩子们了
You should have seen Roger and the girls.
我从没见过他们这么开心
I've never seen them so happy.
茄子
Cheese!
他们对我来说就是全部
They mean the world to me.
把你的手平放在桌子上
Put your hand flat on the desk.
然后拿开
Yeah, and take it off.
好了
Here we go.
看到了吗
See?
这能让我们看到肉眼看不见的东西
It just reveals to us what the naked eye can't see.
高科技 对吧
Pretty far out, isn't it?
是啊 真时髦
Yeah, it's groovy.
Drew 你帮Brad备好摄像机了吗
Drew, you got the Bolex ready for Brad?
好了 准备就绪 先生
Yeah, already locked and loaded, sir.
怎么了 人有三急嘛
What? I had to go.
所有的房间信号都正常
All the rooms are coming in pretty good.
很好
Good.
瓶子里是什么
What's in the bottle?
圣水
Holy water.
放一些宗教信物
Presence of religious icons..
会让非圣洁之物起反应
..Will get a reaction from anything unholy.
激怒它们
Sort of pisses them off.
所以我满屋子都放了这些
So I set these throughout the house,
看看能不能弄起点动静
see if I can stir things up a bit.
- 就像对着吸血鬼亮出十字架  - 没错
Like holding a cross to a vampire? Yeah. Exactly.
其实我不太信吸血鬼的存在
Except I don't believe in vampires.
不是我
Wasn't me.
Brad 去拿相机
Brad, get the camera.
好了
Okay.
现在是九点十八分 我们要
All right, it's 9:18, we're headed down
下去地窖了 刚刚那儿的门自己打开了
into the cellar where the door's just opened on its own.
和我在一起的有Lorraine和Brad警官
I have Lorraine and Officer Brad Hamilton with me.
保持地窖灯光关闭状态
Let's keep the cellar light off.
如果想跟我们交流 就来点动静吧
Give us a sign that you wanna communicate with us.
亲爱的 你还好吗
Hon, you all right?
这里绝对有点什么
There's definitely something here.
- 好吧 关上门 弄点动静出来 - 3我手好冰
All right, close the door. Move something. My hands are so cold.
快来
Come on.
不
No.
它走了
It's gone. It's gone.
我什么都没拍到
I got nothing.
好吧
Okay.
就像我说的 并不是每次都能如愿以偿
Well, like I said, it doesn't always work when you want it to.
或许摄像机有拍到点什么
Yeah, maybe the camera picked something up.
小心
Watch out!
作为一个不相信鬼灵的人
For a guy who doesn't believe..
门猛地关上的时候你有点吓蒙了
..You looked a little freaked out when that door slammed shut.
肯定是室内风
It must have been a draft.
真有意思
Oh, that's funny.
风从来不会让我露出那种表情
A draft never put that look on my face before.
我更相信钟
I believe the clock.
三点零八了
It's 308.
让我看看你的眼镜
Let me see your glasses.
给你的
For you.
我等等想带姑娘们
I think I might take some girls
出去吃冰淇淋 觉得怎么样
for ice cream later on. What do you say about that?
- 好耶  - 亲爱的 你想来吗
- Yeah! - Honey, you wanna come?
我累死了 要去睡一会
I'm exhausted. I'm just gonna take a nap.
熬了几个夜困死我了
The late nights are getting to me.
好主意 你去歇歇吧
That's probably a good idea. Why don't you get some rest.
- Lorraine和我会照看一切的  - 真的吗
Lorraine and I'll watch over things for a bit. Really?
我要走了 一小时我轮班
I'm gonna take off. I have a shift starting in an hour.
家里好久没这样了
The house hasn't felt like this in a long time.
有你们在孩子们好像安心多了
I think the kids feel a lot safer with you around.
- 我能习惯这样  - 什么 我洗衣服吗
I could get used to this. What, me doing laundry?
你真幽默
Hahaha. You're funny.
不 我是说这地方
No, this place.
乡下新鲜的空气
Nice, fresh country air.
他们有个幸福的家 不是吗
They have such a beautiful family, don't they?
最小的那个 April 看见她给我煎饼的样子了吗
Yeah, that little one, April, did you see her bring me pancakes?
我们必须帮他们
We've gotta help them.
我知道
I know.
从修好雪佛兰开始
I'll start with the Chevy.
Carolyn
Carolyn!
你还好吗
Are you okay?
Carolyn 开门
Carolyn, open the door.
Carolyn 快开门
Carolyn, open up!
你还好吗
Are you okay?
- 我没事  - 你病了吗
Oh, I'm fine. Are you sick?
- 我醒来想吐 仅此而已  - 我好像看到
I woke up feeling nauseous, that's all. I thought I saw..
Roger和孩子们好像回来了
I hear Roger and the girls.
稍等
One minute.
- 你们想玩游戏吗  - 无聊
Guys, do you wanna play a game? Boring!
谢谢老爸
Thank you, Daddy.
进去吧
Let's go inside.
我就觉得是你
I thought that was you.
你不介意吧
Hey, I hope you don't mind.
我在史密斯菲尔德
I got a good deal on a
废车场低价买了个组装件
rebuild at that wrecking yard in Smithfield.
- 不介意 你看上很精通 - 是啊等着看吧
No, you look like you know what you're doing. Yeah, we'll see.
你这儿真不错 Roger
Got a nice place here, Roger.
Lorraine和我总想在乡下买个房子
Lorraine and I always wanted a spot in the country.
这套卖你啊
I'll sell you this one.
给我递个扳手好吗
Hey, hand me a wrench, would you?
你们能来对我们来说真是意义重大
Hey, uh, it really means a lot to us to have you here.
我承认 我之前不太相信这些
I gotta admit, I was a little bit skeptical going in.
只是想跟你道个谢 谢谢你们做的一切
Just wanna say thank you, though, for coming out when you did.
不是我的功劳 是Lorraine
I can't take the credit. That's, uh.. That's all Lorraine.
- 我并不想的  - 为什么
I didn't want to. Oh. Why's that?
Lorraine看到的 感受到的 摸到的 帮到了人
Whatever Lorraine sees, feels, touches, it helps people.
但同时也给她带来了伤害
But it also takes a toll on her.
每次一点一点侵袭
Little piece each time.
几个月前我们在着手一个案子
Couple months ago we were working on a case.
她看到了一些东西
She saw something.
那次造成了很大的伤害
It took a real big piece.
我们回到家的时候
When we got home..
她进了房间 把自己反锁在里面
..She went into our room, locked herself in..
不说话 不进食 整整在里面待了八天
..Didn't talk, didn't eat, didn't come out for eight days.
她看到了什么
What'd she see?
滚出去
Get out of here!
我不知道
I don't know.
我也不会问
And I won't ask.
我再去倒点 你要吗
I need to reload. You want some?
不用了谢谢
I'm good, thanks.
好吧
All right.
看看她都逼我做了什么
Look what she made me do.
嘿
Hey.
Ed
Ed?
看看她都逼我做了什么
Look what she made me do!
Ed 快来
Ed! Ed!
Ed
Ed!
伙计 你还好吗
Dude, you okay?
别急 Brad 怎么了
Hold up, Brad. What's going on?
我看到了个人 一个穿着女仆装的女人
I saw someone. There was a woman dressed as a maid.
Ed 有东西了
Ed? Ed, we're getting something.
- 是Cindy 她在梦游  - 不 我们需要这个
It's just Cindy. She's sleepwalking. No, wait. We need this.
为什么要拍Cindy
Why do we need pictures of Cindy?
不是她触发的
She didn't trigger it.
- 你什么意思  - 有东西跟着她
What do you mean she didn't trigger it? Somebody's with her.
谁
Who?
Cindy
Cindy!
过来 这里安全
Hey, over here. It's safe.
有东西跟她在一起
There's someone else in there with her.
我听到其他声音了 给 你听
I'm hearing another voice. Here, listen.
跟我走 这边
Follow me. This way.
这是我躲的地方
This is where I hide.
Cindy
Cindy?
她去哪了 Ed
Where'd she go, Ed?
窗户锁着
Windows are locked.
Ed 她去哪了
Ed, where'd she go?
Brad 把紫外灯拿来
Brad, get the UV light.
- 什么东西  - 问Drew
The what? Just ask Drew.
Drew 我需要紫外灯
Drew, I need a UV light. Uh..
就这个 快去快去
Here, that's it. Go, go, go, go!
把灯关了
Turn off the light.
别挡着道
Get out of the way.
好了
Okay.
开灯
Hit the lights!
找到她了
Found her.
好了
Here we go.
- 抱好了吗  - 嗯
All right. You got her? Yeah.
Rory害怕的时候就藏那儿
That's where Rory hides when he's afraid.
亲爱的 把April的音乐盒给我
Hon? Could I have April's music box, please?
- Cindy怎么样了 - 她什么都不记得了
How's Cindy? She doesn't remember a thing.
给你
Here you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
Lorraine
Lorraine!
不
No.
Lorraine
Lorraine!
是她逼我的
She made me do it.
Ed
Ed!
拜托 Lorraine
Come on! Lorraine!
Ed
Ed!
Ed 我知道她做了什么了
Ed, I know what she did.
- 好了 没事了  - 我知道她做了什么
I got you. I know. It's okay. I know what she did.
我知道她做了什么 她附身在母亲身上杀了孩子
I know what she did. She possessed the mother to kill the child.
她每晚都去找Carolyn
She visits Carolyn every night.
所以才会有那些淤青 她在蚕食她
That's what the bruise marks are! She's feeding off of her!
Nancy
Nancy?
Nancy!
你还好吗
Are you okay?
Nancy
Nancy!
抓住她
Grab her!
爸爸 救命
Daddy! Help!
Nancy
Nancy!
她还好吗
Is she okay?
没事了 有我
It's okay, I got you.
拍到了吗
Did you get that?
拍到了
Yeah.
我把底片拿去冲洗 然后给Gordon神父
I'll have the footage developed and get it over to Father Gordon.
他是我们在教堂的联络人
He's our liaison at the church.
所以大概很快就会有回应
I imagine we'll get a pretty fast response.
- 听着 Roger  - 怎么了
Listen, Roger? Yeah?
我们接到驱魔人后 我会回来 但Lorraine
Listen, when we get the exorcist, I'll be back. But Lorraine..
- 我理解  - 在这之前Drew会照看你们的
Yeah, I understand. Until then, Drew's gonna keep an eye on you.
- Ed 感谢你做的一切  - 没事
Hey, Ed, thank you for everything. Yeah.
妈妈
Mommy?
就这些了
That's everything.
妈妈
Mommy?
Judy
Judy?
天哪
Oh, God!
Judy
Judy?
Lorraine 等等
Lorraine! Wait!
Lorraine 怎么了
Lorraine. What?
妈 是我 Judy没事吧
Mom, it's me. Is Judy okay?
- 怎么了  - 你能去看看吗 拜托
What? Can you go check, please?
该死 妈 你就去看看啦
Damn it, Mom, just check, please!
- 你打算告诉我发生什么了吗  - 是Judy
Are you gonna tell me what's going on? It's Judy.
你什么意思
What? What do you mean?
怎么了
What?
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
妈 抱歉 我不是有意吓你的
Mom, I'm sorry, I didn't mean to scare you.
我等等再跟你解释 好吗
I'll explain later, okay?
到底发生什么了
What the hell happened?
我看到Judy在水里
I had a vision of Judy in the water.
我知道肯定是某种警告
I know it was some kind of warning.
我知道
I know it.
好的
Okay.
我们走吧
Let's get out of here.
- 所以呢  - 好吧 你可真不是开玩笑的
So? Yeah, well, you weren't kidding.
不是
No.
Ed 情况有点复杂 因为那些孩子没有洗礼
Look, Ed, this is complicated because the kids aren't baptized.
- 不 我理解  - 然后那家人也不是教会成员
No, I understand. And the family, are not members of the church.
- 别这样  - 所以
Oh, come on. And..
许可必须从梵蒂冈(教皇所在)直接下达
The approval would have to come directly from the Vatican.
神父 我们从没见过这样的
Father, we've never seen nothing like this.
我也是
Yeah, well, neither have I.
神父 他们没多少时间了
Father, they don't have a lot of time.
好吧
All right.
我会亲自跟进的
I'll push it through myself.
- 多谢了 神父 谢谢  - 谢谢你
Thank you, Father. Thank you. Thank you.
- 那我们等你电话  - 好
All right, we'll wait for your call. Yeah.
妈妈 爸爸
Mommy? Daddy?
妈妈
Mommy?
爸爸
Daddy?
Dad?
奶奶
Nanna?
Nanna!
奶奶 救命 奶奶
Nanna, help! Nanna, help!
Judy
Judy?
奶奶
Nanna!
救命
Help!
- Judy  - 奶奶
Judy! Nanna!
- Judy 开门  - 妈妈
Judy, open the door! Mom!
- Ed 有点不对劲  - 什么
Ed, there's something wrong. What?
奶奶
Nanna!
- Judy  - 救命
Judy! Help!
- Judy 快开门  - 怎么了
Judy! Judy, open this door! What is it?
- 她怎么了 Judy  - 快 快 快
What's wrong with her? Judy! Hey, move. Move, move, move, move.
Judy 往后站 亲爱的
Judy, get back, honey. Get back!
快点
Come on! Hurry.
救命
Help! Help!
离门远点 Judy
Get away from the door, Judy!
天 你还好吗
Oh, God! Are you okay?
有个人在和安娜贝尔一起摇椅子
There was someone rocking in the chair with Annabelle.
什么
What?
没事了
It's okay.
她还在柜子里
She's still in the case.
没事了
It's okay.
已经没事了
It's okay. It's okay.
爸爸 爸爸
Dad! Dad! Daddy!
爸爸 妈妈带着Christine和April一起走了
Dad! Dad! Mom just left with Christine and April.
她就这么开车走了 我不知道怎么回事
She went in the car and drove away. I don't know what happened.
她闻起来就像腐肉 也不说怎么了就走了
She smells like rotting meat. She didn't say what was going on.She just left.
你什么意思 她走了 去哪了
What do you mean, she left? Left where?
我也不知道她去哪
Gone! I don't know where she was going.
妈 我们要去哪
Where are we going, Mom?
喂 我是Roger
Hello? It's Roger.
Carolyn有点不对劲
Somethings going on with Carolyn.
Andrea说Carolyn带着Christine和April走了
Andrea was here, said Carolyn took off with Christine and April.
还说她闻起来像腐肉
The girls said she smelled like rotten meat...
她附身在母亲身上
She possesses the mother..
杀孩子 她就是这么做的
..To kill the child, that's what she does.
她要把他们带去那房子
She's taking them to the house.
Roger快回去房子那 我和你在那碰面
Roger, get back to the house now. I'll meet you.
锁上门 拉上窗帘 别接电话
Lock the door, close the blinds. Stay off the phone!
快走
Go.
- 我跟你一起去  - 不 你和Judy待一起
I'm coming. No, you stay with Judy.
保护Judy唯一的方式就是终结这一切
Only way to protect Judy is if we stop this where it started.
否则 她又会缠上我们
Otherwise, she'll latch onto us again.
所以我才要去
That's exactly why I am going.
你以为我会让你一个人去吗
You think I'm gonna let you walk into this alone?
我不能失去你
I can't lose you.
不会的
You won't.
我们一起来结束这一切
Let's finish this together.
- 锁上了 - Carolyn
Agh! It's locked. Carolyn!
Roger
Roger!
让开
Get out of the way!
- Roger - Ed
Roger! Ed!
- Carolyn  - Ed
Carolyn! Ed!
- Carolyn  - 我们在下面
Carolyn! We're down here!
Carolyn 别 不不 她有...
Carolyn, don't! No, no! She's got...
抓住她的手 去拿剪刀
Get her hand! Get the scissors!
- 得把她弄到车子里去  - 然后带去哪
We gotta get her to the car! And bring her where?
带她去牧师那驱魔
To take her to the priest for the exorcism.
- April呢 - April
Where's April? April?
April
April!
把Christine带去车子那 找到April
Take Christine to the car and find April!
April
April!
快
Come on!
- 她不会让她离开房子的  - 你什么意思
She won't let her leave the house. What do you mean?
如果我们带走她 女巫会杀了她的
If we take her out, the witch will kill her. Agh!
Roger
Roger!
Carolyn
Carolyn!
走
Go!
Carolyn
Carolyn?
好了 你先进去 快点
Okay, I'm gonna put you in here. Come on.
- 进去 待着  - 我不想一个人在这
Get in. Stay in here. I don't wanna stay here by myself.
不管发生什么别出来 我会回来的
Stay in here no matter what. I'll be back.
我得去找April 我会回来的 我保证
I have to find April, okay? I'll be back, I promise.
April
April?
你还好吗
You Okay?
住手
Stop!
Brad Brad
Brad! Brad!
拿点东西把她绑住
Let's get something to tie her up!
按住
Hold it.
我得打给Gordon神父 得让他过来
I gotta call Father Gordon. We gotta get Father Gordon out here.
太远了 她撑不住的 看看她
He's too far away. She won't make it. Look at her.
- 你得走了  - 你说什么呢
Then you need to leave. What are you talking about?
我来驱魔
I have to do it. The exorcism.
什么 你不是说要个牧师吗 你又不是
What? I thought you said we need a priest. You're not a priest.
- 你还有更好的主意吗  - 他可以的
Well, you got a better idea? He can do it.
- 你可以的  - 但你得出去
You can do it. But you gotta get out of here.
- 我不会离开你的  - 该死 Lorraine
I'm not leaving you! Damn it, Lorraine
你不能在这儿
I'm not doing this with you in here!
上帝让我们走到一起是有原因的 此刻就是
God brought us together for a reason. This is it.
我去拿书
I'm gonna get the book.
April
April!
以圣父 圣子 圣灵之名
"In the name of the Father, the Son, the Holy Spirit."
April
April!
按住她 按住她
Hold her still! Hold her still!
过来 按住她
Come here! Hold her still!
April
April?
April!
April 你在下面吗
April, you under there?
April
April!
Carolyn 不要放弃 不要让她掌控你
Carolyn. Carolyn. Don't give in! Don't let her take you!
Ed 你得停下 你要杀了她了 停下
Ed! You gotta stop, you're killing her. Stop!
不能停
No, he can't!
Roger 救我
Roger, help me!
Ed 该死的 快停下
Ed! Goddamn it, stop it!
你不懂 我们是为了她的灵魂
You don't understand this! We are now fighting for her soul!
以耶稣 圣人 天使之名
"In the name of Jesus Christ, the saints and all the angels..
我命令你展现你的真面目
..I command you to reveal yourself!"
Roger 救我
Roger, help me!
放她下来
Put her down!
Carolyn
Carolyn!
Ed 小心
Ed, look out! Unh!
你还好吗
Are you okay?
按住她 别让她再回来
Hold her still! Don't let her up!
她快不行了 Roger
We're losing her, Roger!
去你的 离我家人远点 听到了吗
Damn you! You leave my family alone, you hear me?
我不知道你是什么
I don't know what you are,
但你离我妻子远点 该死的
but you leave my wife alone, goddamn it!
放了她 你听到了吗 放了她
Let her go! Do you hear me? Let her go!
放了她 该死的 放了她
Let her go, goddamn it! Let her go!
她已经死了
She's already gone.
而你们也都要死了
And now you're all gonna die.
April
April!
我找到她了 她在房子下面 厨房下面
I found her! She's under the house! Under the kitchen!
不 不要
Don't! No!
抓住她
Get her!
给 Carolyn
Here. Carolyn!
- Carolyn - 她在洞里 就这
Carolyn! She's in that hole. Right there.
Carolyn 上帝啊 不
Carolyn? Oh, my God. No!
进不去 够不着啊
Can't go in. Can't reach.
不 Carolyn 别
No! Carolyn, don't!
Carolyn 不要
Carolyn, no!
Bathsheba
Bathsheba!
以上帝赐我之力 我命你重回地狱
By the power of God, I condemn you back to hell!
这是你女儿
This is your daughter!
你不能屈服
You can't give in! Agh!
Roger 我们得让她自己反抗
Roger. We need to get her to fight from the inside.
别让她得逞 别让这邪物得逞
Don't let her do this. Don't let this thing do this.
你要反抗 我知道你比她强大
You gotta fight it. I konw you're stronger than she is.
- 你得反抗  - 继续 Roger
You gotta fight! Keep it going, Roger!
别离开我们 好吗 回来 Carolyn
You gotta stay with us, all right? Come on back, Carolyn.
没错就是这样 把她弄回来
You're in that's it! Get her back!
- 记得你给我看的吗  - 不
Remember what you showed me. No!
记得你说过你永远不会忘的那一天
Remember that day that you said you would never forget.
你说他们对你来说就是全部
You said they meant the world to you.
这些你都不要了吗
This is what you'll be leaving behind.
妈妈
Mommy?
结束了
It's over.
我真抱歉
I am so sorry.
我好爱你 我太爱你了
I love you so much. I love you so much.
我好爱你
I love you so much.
我太高兴了
I'm so happy.
看你这表情 又是风吗
A draft do that to your face?
我宁愿每天面对持枪匪徒
I'd take a guy with a gun any day.
你干得很好
You did good.
不 你才是
No, you did.
我打给Gordon神父告诉他发生的一切
I'll call Father Gordon and let him know what happened.
去吧
Sounds good.
梵蒂冈许可这次驱魔了
The Vatican approved the exorcism.
来的真是时候
Heh. Nice timing.
如果可以的话 他明天想见见我们
And if we can, then he'd like to meet with us tomorrow.
他想跟我们聊聊一个在长岛的案件
There's a case in Long Island he'd like to discuss.
真的吗
Really?
恶魔的力量是强大的 这些力量永远存在
直至今日 童话是真的 恶魔存在 上帝也存在
对与我们人类来说 命运就取决于我们决意跟随何者